question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after "
                     "being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous "
                     "actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety "
                     "by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
    ]
}
